{
    "subject": "resource/Murder,_My_Sweet",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Detective_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Murder, My Sweet is Detective films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7934691309928894,
            "question": "What are some popular examples of detective films besides 'Murder, My Sweet'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7470737099647522,
            "question": "What genre of film is 'Murder, My Sweet'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5012086629867554,
            "question": "Does 'Murder, My Sweet' involve a mystery to be solved?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4436745047569275,
            "question": "Who typically directs detective films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4341769516468048,
            "question": "What type of character is the protagonist in 'Murder, My Sweet'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3667147755622864,
            "question": "Are there common themes found in detective films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3625333905220032,
            "question": "What is the typical setting for a detective film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26080384850502014,
            "question": "How has the portrayal of detectives changed over time in film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25137099623680115,
            "question": "Why are detective films so enduringly popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17728394269943237,
            "question": "What era are most detective films set in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Murder, My Sweet is Detective films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6844_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why are detective films so enduringly popular?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6844_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the portrayal of detectives changed over time in film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6844_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the typical setting for a detective film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6844_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6844_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents discuss the film \"Murder, My Sweet\" and describe it as a noir film involving a private detective named Philip Marlowe. This information supports that the subject of \"Murder, My Sweet\" is indeed related to detective films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Murder, My Sweet is primarily a film noir, which is a style of film marked by such elements as cynicism, moral ambiguity, and complex female characters. While it does belong to the detective genre, its focus is more on the atmosphere, themes, and characterization associated with film noir rather than strictly being about detectives.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The subject of Murder, My Sweet is actually Philip Marlowe, a private detective, not Detective films.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}